ireps.gov.in 2012-10-18

# (1)Privacy Policy for www.ireps.gov.in

                                                      (1)
                                Privacy Policy for www.ireps.gov.in
CRIS takes your privacy very seriously.
1. In general, you can visit IREPS website without telling us who you are and without revealing any
information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you in order to
        Conduct the specific on-line transaction that you requested.
        Respond to queries or requests submitted by you.
        Process orders or applications submitted by you.
        Administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us.
        Use of information for the purpose of vendor searches.
        Anticipate and resolve problems with any goods or services supplied to/by you.
        Create interface or services that may meet your needs.
 2. Except as set out in this privacy policy, we will not disclose any personally identifiable information
without your permission unless under the following circumstances:
        We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights
         or defend against legal claims.
        Disclosure to law enforcing agency of the Government on their demand, direction or instruction.
        We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action
         regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical
         safety of any person, or if we believe that such action is necessary to protect and/or defend our
         rights, property or personal safety and those of our users/customers etc or as otherwise required by
         law.
3. Information Collected:
When you visit our portal to browse, read pages, or downloads information, we automatically collect and
store only the following information:
      The Internet domain and IP address from which you access our portal;
      The date and time you access our portal; and
      The pages you visit;
If you do not want any personal or business information collected, please do not submit it to us; however,
without this information we will be unable to process your on-line transaction.
4. Security:
We use safe, tested and quality technology for transmitting the received information so that quality and
privacy of the data is neither impaired nor breached and a variety of security technologies and procedures
like Password, SSL, PKI, Digital Signatures, asymmetric cryptography etc. are applied to protect
personal/business information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.
It is your responsibility to keep your password confidential and Digital Signature Certificate in a secure
manner. Do not share this information with anyone.
We provide you with the facility to view or edit your company’s/personal information and such information
cannot be viewed by others except by authorized CRIS/Railway officials. You will be required to sign in
with your credentials in the prescribed manner as provided on the sites to verify your authenticity.

                                                       (2)
5. Use of your personal information submitted to other websites:
We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites even if:
     You accessed the third party website using links from our website; or
     You linked to our website from a third party website.
We recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit and contact the owner or operator of such
website if you have any concerns or questions.
6. AntiSpam policy:
IREPS reserves the right to reject and/or report any suspicious spam emails, to the authorities concerned,
for necessary action, from time to time.
7. Use of Cookies:
We do not use cookies to track information about a user’s movements throughout our site. However, when
making a purchase, users are redirected to our payment processing service that may use and/or require the
use of cookies for making online transactions.
8. Chats
If at any time this site offers any chat rooms etc. we may collect the information that you disclose. Such
information will be used in accordance with this privacy policy. Please note that we cannot be responsible
for other parties’ use of the personal information which you make available to such third parties through
any chat room etc. on this site. Please be careful about what personal information you disclose in this way
9. Change In Privacy Policy
From time to time we may make changes to this privacy policy. If we make any substantial changes to this
privacy policy and the way in which we use your personal data we will post these changes on this page.
10. Comments and Questions
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please send an email to helpdesk.eps@cris.org.in
or in writing to: Centre For Railway Information Systems, Chankyapuri, New Delhi, PIN – 110021.
                                                    ---------
